(laid back groovy music)
♪ I, I'm so in love with you ♪
♪ Whatever you want to do ♪
♪ Is all right with me ♪
♪ 'Cause you make me feel so brand new ♪
♪ And I want to spend my life with you ♪
♪ Let me say that since, baby,
since we've been together ♪
♪ Ooh, loving you forever ♪
♪ Is what I need ♪
♪ Let me, be the one you come running to ♪
♪ I'll never be untrue ♪
♪ Oh baby ♪
♪ Let's, let's stay together ♪
♪ Lovin' you whether, whether ♪
♪ Times are good or bad, happy or sad ♪
♪ Oh baby ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Whether times are good
or bad, happy or sad ♪
♪ Why, somebody, why people break up ♪
♪ I wanna know, then
turn around and make up ♪
♪ Yeah, I just can't see ♪
♪ But you'd never do that to me ♪
♪ Would you baby ♪
♪ Being around you is all I see ♪
♪ Here's what I want us do ♪
♪ Let's stay together ♪
♪ Loving you whether, whether ♪
♪ Times are good or bad, happy or sad ♪
♪ Let's, woo, let's stay together baby ♪
♪ I wanna love you whether,
whether times are good or bad ♪
♪ Happy or sad ♪
♪ Yeah baby ♪
♪ Let's stay together ♪
♪ I wanna love you whether, whether ♪
♪ Times are good or bad, happy or sad ♪
♪ We can always be with one another ♪
♪ As long as I ♪
♪ As long as I can hold you baby ♪
♪ I wanna squeeze you ♪
♪ Baby, let me be with you baby ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
(audience clapping)